<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <EventText.frenseynomor.c1>You see a familiar person in a lab coat, his hair looks like it hasn't seen a comb in days. Not only that, dark circles under his eyes have deepened and his once-clean lab coat is now wrinkled and stained. Despite his disheveled appearance, a wide grin spreads across his face like he has done something great.</EventText.frenseynomor.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1>Approach the researcher.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.c1>Upon noticing you, his face lights up with recognition and excitement. “Oh, it’s you! You won’t believe this but I’ve finally done it! I’ve completed my research!” He exclaims, almost bouncing on the balls of his feet.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1>“What have you discovered?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.c1>With a flourish, he pulls out a syringe filled with a violet liquid from his pocket. “This…” He says, holding it up like a prized trophy, “Is my newest creation. After countless trials and errors, I have finally perfected the formula. This is the one that will enhance our human capabilities far beyond our current limitations!”
</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1>Examine the drug.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.c1>You take a closer look at the syringe, noting that there is no notable difference between this and the previous substance you encountered before.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Are you sure it’s safe?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>His eyes widen with fervent conviction. “Absolutely! I’ve tested it thoroughly on various specimens and recorded every possible outcome. This time, there’s no margin for error. All I need now is to test it on a live human… In fact, I’m so certain of its safety and efficacy that I’m willing to test it on myself right here and now!” Before you can react, he rolls up his sleeve and prepares to inject himself with the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Hold up… Maybe it’s best not to do it yet.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He pauses, giving you a curious look as he asks, “And why shouldn’t I do it?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What if something goes wrong again?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Tsk! Nothing could go wrong! This time I double checked everything. I am certain that what I synthesize this time will not kill me.” He replies in irritation.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“You’ve come so far. It would be a shame to rush now and risk everything.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>After considering your words, his enthusiasm falters slightly and is replaced by a more thoughtful expression. “You have a point. I’ve come this far, it wouldn’t hurt to triple-check everything. Fine, I’ll conduct a few more tests and ensure absolute perfection.” He lowers the syringe and tucks it back into his pocket.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Continue.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He contemplates. “However, being in an outpost can only provide me with so much. I've tried to advance my research here but the constraints are undeniable. Perhaps it's time I considered a different approach…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He looks up to you and inquires, “Wait, you travel around often right? Would you consider allowing me to join your crew? Working alongside a diverse team could provide the resources and support I need to truly refine my research."</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Sure, we can take you along.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Excellent! Wait, I realized I haven’t formally introduced myself… I am Fren Seynomor. Although I prefer if you call me Dr. Seynomor. It is a pleasure to make your acquaintance.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Welcome on board.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Alright, I'll gather my things and prepare for the journey ahead." He says, excitement evident in his voice. "I can't wait to get my hands on new live specimens!"</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Leave.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Hold up doctor, I have a few questions.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Shoot me the questions. I’ll try to answer them to the best of my abilities.” He replies.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“What’s your purpose for doing all this research?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>His expression grows serious and a spark of determination in his eyes.“My purpose? It’s simple. I want to push the boundaries of human potential. Imagine a world where our bodies can heal almost instantly, where illness and injury are relics of the past. Picture a world where we can breathe underwater and withstand the pressure of the sea without a diving suit.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“I’m striving to create a future where humanity isn’t limited by its physical weaknesses. This research isn’t just about scientific discovery… It’s about changing the course of our evolution and improving the quality of life for everyone.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Are you one of those cultists?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You mean an acolyte of the Church? Yes, I used to be one. But I left their sect some time ago.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Why did you leave?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Because the Church and I do not share the same sentiments. One may argue that both of us have things in common but the Church is driven by religious beliefs and communion with the parasite. I, on the other hand, rely on solid scientific evidence and facts to find a way to harness the parasite’s abilities.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Do you know anything about the Sigil incident?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh? Sigil City, you say? Where did you hear about that?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“A sergeant mentioned it to me.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Interesting... It’s not common for a sergeant to discuss it. Anyway, I do know a few things. I heard that hundreds of people died there because of a husk outbreak. There are also some rumors about it. One story is that some acolytes of the Church got overzealous and infected a group of civilians during a coalition ceremony.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Oh?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“But I also heard that it was the Separatists who infected the civilians and framed the Church for it. Either way, whether that's true or not, I can't say for certain… Since I just overheard it at a bar.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“That’s all I wanted to ask.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“That's enough questions for now.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Do you think people will accept your work?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“That’s a tricky question. Some will see the potential and embrace it, while others will fear the unknown and reject it. Change is always met with resistance, but I’m confident that once I perfect the drug and establish credibility in my work, they’ll see the benefits and acceptance will surely follow.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>"I'm sorry, but we can't take you with us."</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>Disappointment can be seen on his face but he nods understandingly. “I understand. It was a long shot but I had to ask. No matter, I’ll find a way to make it work… Anyway, I must return to my studies. Farewell.” With that, he walks away, already lost in thought.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“What if there's another unforeseen reaction?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Tsk! There won’t be! I have double checked everything. Even though I have not tested it on a human, I am certain that what I synthesize this time won’t kill me.” He replies in irritation.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Alright, go ahead. Let's see if it works.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>You watch as he administers the drug, his face fills with anticipation. Moments pass in tense silence and he begins to mutter observations to himself. “No immediate adverse side effects… No numbness… I feel perfectly fine.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>He pauses, looking at his hands and then his arms. “I didn’t turn! This is great news! However, there is only one way to find out if the drug is truly successful…” He turns to look at you and says, “Come punch me in the face!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“Are you sure about that?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Oh come on, you don’t think I forgot the last time you punched me in the face! You left me with a bruised cheek for a few days straight! Now if my drug works, it won’t hurt as much as before. In fact, the bruise should heal in minutes, according to my data.” He claps his hands together and then spreads them wide as he continues, “Let’s not waste time, punch me! I can handle it!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Punch him in the face.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>You take a deep breath, pull back your fist and deliver a solid punch to his face. His head snaps back and you hear a sickening crack as his nose breaks. He staggers backward, clutching his face as blood starts to pour from his nostrils. “Ahh! Oh god!” He yelps, his voice muffled by his hands.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Did I punch too hard?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Still leaning his head forward with one hand pinching the bridge of his nose, he raises the other hand towards you, waving it dismissively as he says, “No no… You did fine. Just wasn’t expecting you to go for the nose but that’s fine… I’ll just need a moment.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Okay."</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He grabs his broken nose and in a quick motion, snaps it back in place. He grimaces and looks up at you, his eyes watering but then a grin slowly spreads across his face. “This will heal quickly… Just wait and see. The bleeding should stop any minute now…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Wait patiently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Few minutes pass and his confident grin starts to falter as the blood continues to trickle from his nose. He furrows his brow with frustration and confusion. “This… doesn’t make sense.” He mumbles, his voice tinged with irritation. “The bleeding should have stopped by now… Why isn’t it working?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I don’t know.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He fumbles through his lab coat to grab a cloth to staunch the bleeding, his expression growing more exasperated by the moment. “I don’t understand. The regenerative properties… They should be active.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Maybe the drug didn’t work?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“No… It did work but maybe not in the way I expected. I've noticed that the first aid I applied isn’t as effective as it should be. It seems the drug might be interfering with the healing process.” He answers as he analyzes his condition.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He sighs heavily, “It seems like I have to conduct some tests on myself to find out the true effects of the drug… It may not be a complete success, but it’s not a total failure either since I’m still alive. I have to further my research again with the knowledge I gained.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Do you want another punch?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>Still leaning his head forward with one hand pinching the bridge of his nose, he raises the other hand towards you, shaking it as he says, “No, I think one punch is enough... I need to… Just give me a moment.” He mutters, trying to compose himself.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>Refuse to punch him.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>“Of course! If my drug works, a simple punch won’t cause me much pain. Normally, a bruise would take days to heal but with this drug, it should heal in minutes! If my information is correct...” He claps his hands together and then spreads them wide as he continues, “Come on, enough chatters… Punch me! I can take it!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>He rolls his eyes and sighs, “You growing soft on me? I thought you had a knack for punching people…” He pulls out a knife from his pocket and continues, “Tsk… Whatever. If you won’t help, I’ll do it myself.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>He presses the sharp blade against his palm and slashes it. He winces as blood begins to pour from the wound. “Now, pay close attention. The bleeding should stop on its own within a minute and if the drug works as intended, the wound should heal completely within a few minutes without any intervention.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>Watch carefully.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>A few minutes have passed and despite his confident words, the bleeding shows no sign of slowing down. The wound remains open, the edges raw and unhealed. He frowns, frustration and confusion etched across his face. He mutters under his breath, “This… This doesn’t make sense. It should have stopped by now… Why isn’t it working?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>He fumbles through his lab coat to grab a bandage and begin wrapping it around his hand to staunch the bleeding while his expression grows more exasperated by the moment. “I don’t understand. The regenerative properties… They should be active.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“No… It did work but maybe not in the way I expected.” He holds up his injured hand, showing you the bandage now soaked with crimson blood, despite the pressure he's applied. “I've noticed that the first aid I applied isn’t as effective as it should be. It seems the drug might be interfering with the healing process.” He explains as he studies his condition intently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c2>He rolls his eyes and sighs, “Tsk… Whatever. I guess you don’t want to hurt yourself, which is fine.” He pulls out a knife from his pocket and continues, “If you won’t help, I’ll do it myself.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o2>Leave the man alone.</EventText.frenseynomor.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.c2>You spot a familiar figure in a lab coat scanning the crowd. Despite his messy hair and baggy eyes revealing sleep deprivation, the man looks anxious… As if he is glancing around for someone or something.</EventText.frenseynomor.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.c1>"Oh? Hello, it’s you again. Quite a coincidence… You’ve come at a perfect time, I need some assistance." The researcher greets you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1>“What do you need?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.c1>He pulls out a syringe filled with purplish liquid from his pocket and replies, “I have been working on my research lately and I’ve managed to synthesize this new drug. Now all I need is someone to test it for me.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.c1>You take a closer look at the syringe and realize you’ve somehow seen this before. Based on what you remember, the appearance of the drug fits the description of the notes you read a while back. You suspect whatever is inside this syringe may contain a husk parasite.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1>“Isn’t this a husk parasite?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>He glances around before leaning closer and whispering, “Shh… Not so loud! We don't want to attract attention… But to answer your question, yes. I need you to inject it into a healthy subject. Like someone trained and strong... The security officers here would be perfect.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What the hell is wrong with you?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He scoffs at your remark, “What do you mean? What I’m doing here is for the greater good of humanity! To find ways to evolve and overcome the limitations of a human body, to adapt ourselves to the harsh environment of Europa.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“No, that’s messed up. I’m not doing it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Tsk… Fine, I'll handle it myself. Somehow I thought you might grasp the significance of my work, but I guess not." With that, he walks away to find someone else.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“And what do I get in return if I choose to help you?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>“What do I get in return if I help you?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He sighs, as if anticipating your question. "I’ll pay you generously if you can do it and gather the results for me."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Alright, I’ll do it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>He hands you the syringe and continues, "I’ll be here waiting. Remember, take note of any notable symptoms. Though I'm confident there won't be any issues."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>You find a security officer doing patrols.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Go up to the officer.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Do you need something?” The officer asks.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Hey! Your doctor wants me to pass you this syringe.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Huh? Really? Usually my doctor will deliver it to me personally… I find it odd that they would ask someone else to do it.” He replies.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Uh… They are busy lately, so they couldn’t meet you.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh… Okay.” He says but before he grabs the syringe, he asks with a hint of skepticism, "Wait, just to be sure, what's my doctor's name?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Dr. Happy.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He nods and replies, “Cool, checks out.” Then he takes the syringe from you and asks, "So, what's in it anyway?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I don’t know. They didn’t tell me but they did say you should take it immediately.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“And why do I need to do that?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Uh… To ensure its effectiveness. They were very specific about the timing.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh okay, if that’s the case...” He murmurs, lifting the syringe to his upper arm and injecting it. "If that's all, I'll get back to work... But let Dr. Happy know I'll visit soon." With that, he turns to leave but you notice him starting to stumble.
</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Continue observing the officer.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Without warning, his limbs jerk erratically and you witness a stinger-like appendage erupting from his mouth as he collapses to the ground, convulsing violently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Time to run and report back to the researcher.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You're back! Now tell me, did the drug work? Was the experiment a success?” The researcher asks eagerly.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I wasn’t able to do it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The researcher sighs in disappointment. “I see.... No matter, do tell me you still have my syringe?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“About that… I lost it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>His face darkens. "You... lost it? Do you have any idea how difficult it was to create that? This sets my research back immensely! I can't believe this...”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He takes a deep breath, clearly frustrated. "I'll have to start from scratch. I can't believe I entrusted this to someone so careless. Now leave me, I have no use for you anymore."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Hand over the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>"Good, at least it's not lost." He takes the syringe, examining it thoughtfully. "This is a setback, but not the end. I'll have to find another way to test it. For now, you should leave. I need to rethink my approach."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Yes… If you count turning into a husk as successful.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Damn it, that wasn't supposed to happen! Based on my calculations, it should have enhanced them, not turned them!” He exclaims, frustration evident in his voice.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Whatever your drug did, it turned them into husks almost instantly.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>"That's impossible… What went wrong? I was sure I added the right components… Unless the husk genetics overpowered the human DNA… Which it shouldn’t, considering the precautions I took...” He mutters, pulling out his notebook and scribbling notes furiously.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>He looks up, realizing he forgot something. "Oh right, your payment for helping me." He says, handing you a handful of mks.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Take the money.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Now do excuse me, I need to return to my research at once.” He utter. With that, the researcher scurries away to somewhere.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>“It doesn't matter anymore. I helped you, now give me my reward.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>He sighs in annoyance, “You did fulfill your end of the bargain, so here.” He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>“Now do excuse me, I must return to my research at once.” He utter. With that, the researcher scurries away to somewhere.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>“No, they turn into a husk.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>“Were they supposed to turn into a husk?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>He looks at you, confused. "No… Wait, they turned into a husk?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>“Yes and almost immediately too.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>“Damn it, that wasn't supposed to happen! Based on my calculations, it should have enhanced them, not turned them!” He exclaims in frustration.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>“You’re telling me you knew this from the start?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.c1>"Well… Yes and no. The sample I created was a modified version of the parasite. It was intended to improve their healing and physical strength. But based on what you said, it seems all it did was accelerate the parasite's control over the host." He explains, pulling out his notebook.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>"What could have gone wrong? I was so sure it worked on crawlers… Unless the reaction differs between species…" He mutters, flipping through his notes.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I helped you, now give me my reward.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He stops flipping through his notes and sighs. "Right, you did your part, so here." He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2>“You almost got me killed! I expect compensation for this!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He sighs loudly, "Given the situation, I understand your frustration. Fine, I’ll add a bonus to your payment… Since you did fulfill your end of the bargain." He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>He sighs in annoyance, “You’ll find what I give sufficient as compensation.” He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5>Punch the researcher.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.c1>Your knuckles connect with a satisfying thud against his cheekbone, sending him stumbling backward. His eyes widen in shock and pain as he clutches his face, a red mark already starting to form. “Ouch… What was that for?” He asks with a puzzled look.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1>“You almost got me killed!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.c1>“What did you mean? How could I have gotten you killed?” He queries while rubbing the bruised side of his cheeks.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1>“Whatever you gave me turned the guy into a husk!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.c1>"Impossible! That wasn’t supposed to happen! I was sure I made it right! Unless the husk genetics are too overpowering… Which they shouldn’t be with the precautions I took..."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1>“You knew this from the start?!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Well… Yes and no. The sample I created was a modified version of the parasite. It was intended to improve their healing and physical strength. But based on what you said, it seems all it did was accelerate the parasite's control over the host." He explains, ignoring the pain on his cheeks as he pulls out his notebook.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1>“You monster! You used me for this!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"What I did here could help humanity evolve! This is for the greater good! You may call me a monster but you accepted the job without question. Now you’re no different from me, your hands are stained with blood too." He snaps at you while flipping through his notebook, seemingly trying to find something in it.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I'm not letting you leave here alive.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He pauses, stuffing his notebook into his lab coat before swiftly drawing a knife. With frustration in his voice, he declares, "Tsk… And I won't let you interfere with my work!"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Time to fight.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Whatever, I want out of here. Give me my damn reward.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He sighs in annoyance, “Tsk... Despite the punch and your insults, you did fulfill your end of the bargain, so here.” He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Whatever, I helped you, now give me my reward.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He sighs in annoyance, “Despite the punch, you did your part, so here.” He pulls out a handful of mks and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o2>“You lied to me!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o2.c1>"What are you talking about?" He queries as he rubs the sore spot on his cheek.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>Suddenly, his limbs twitch uncontrollably. You watch in horror as a stinger-like appendage bursts from his mouth. His body collapses to the ground and convulses violently. Realization dawns on you as you understand the true nature of the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Time to run and find the researcher.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Um… They said it's to stabilize your condition until they can see you personally.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Dr. Paine.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>"I don't know any doctor by that name. I think you have the wrong person." The officer replies.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Apologize and leave.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>Brazenly inject the officer with the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>Tired of the act, you lunge at the officer with the syringe. Startled, he grabs your wrist to stop you but you manage to jab the syringe into his neck. He shoves you away, eyes wide with shock. "What did you just inject me with?!"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1>Give a nervous laugh.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>He places a hand on his neck, swaying and struggling to stay on his feet. He tries to grab you but struggles to keep steady as his limbs twitch erratically.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1>Take a step back.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c1>He attempts to speak but before he can get the words out, a stinger-like appendage bursts out from his mouth and his body collapses to the floor, convulsing violently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c2>You watch in horror as a stinger-like appendage bursts out of his mouth. His body collapses to the floor and convulses violently. Realization dawns on you as you understand the true nature of the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>Tired of putting up the act, you lunge at the officer with the syringe, attempting to jab the syringe into his neck. However, he reacts quickly by grabbing your wrist and twisting it painfully. The syringe slips from your grasp and clatters to the floor, rolling out of reach. The officer tightens his grip and his eyes narrow in suspicion. "What do you think you're doing?" He demands.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2>Attempt to break free and flee.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2.c1>You kick the officer in the knee, causing him to curse in pain and loosens his grip on you. Taking advantage of the moment, you break free and dash away.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2.o1>Time to run!</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>“Dr. Sei.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>“Dr. Wilson.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Hey! There’s something behind you!”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>The officer turns around to look at where you have pointed. Seizing the opportunity, you quickly and stealthily inject the syringe into his upper arm. He winces slightly from the sudden pain and turns back to you with confusion in his eyes.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>"Ow, what was that? Did you do something?" He asks, eyeing you suspiciously as he inspects his arm, trying to figure out what just happened.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“No? Did something happen?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“No, I thought I felt something… Must have been my imagination. Anyway, what did you see?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“I thought I saw a clown.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Seriously? Why did you stop me for that? They are literally everywhere. Now if you got nothing else to say, scram.” He states while walking away. Although, you notice his movements are sluggish and he seems to be stumbling on his own feet.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Are you okay?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“I thought I saw someone suspicious holding a gun.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Really? If that’s the case, I’ll go check it out.” He states, turning around and heading down the hallway. Though you notice his movements are sluggish and he seems to be stumbling on his own feet.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>The officer tries to speak but his body begins to twitch in an irregular manner as his limbs begin to twist themselves in a weird direction. Next thing you know, a stinger-like appendage bursts out of his mouth as his body collapses to the floor and begins to spasm.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>The officer tries to speak but his body twitches uncontrollably and his limbs contorting in unnatural directions. Your eyes widen in shock as a stinger-like appendage suddenly bursts out of his mouth. His body collapses to the floor and spasms violently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>“I thought I saw a mudraptor tapping on the window.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>“Really? Could have sworn that the clean-up crew cleared the mudraptors near the outpost like a few days ago but I guess they probably left a few stragglers roaming about. I’ll inform the administrator about–” Before he can finish his sentence, you notice him swaying and struggling to stay up on his feet.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>The officer turns around to look at where you have pointed. Just as you move to inject the syringe into his arm, he unexpectedly glances back at you and notices the syringe in your hand. His eyes widen as he quickly grabs your wrist, stopping the needle from piercing his skin. "What do you think you're doing?" He demands, his grip tightening as he assesses the situation.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>"It’s a new procedure to test your reflexes. And uh… You passed!"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>“Do you think I'm that gullible? Now you're under arrest!” With that, he pulls out his stun baton and prepares to arrest you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>Attempt to forcefully inject the officer.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>You wrestle with the officer and through sheer force, you manage to jab the syringe into his neck. He stares at you in horror and shoves you away. He yanks the syringe out and exclaims, "What did you just inject me with?!"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>You struggle with the officer and attempt to jab the syringe into his neck. However, he anticipates your move and shifts your hand to the side, twisting your wrist painfully. The syringe falls to the ground and rolls out of reach. The officer glares at you and with his grip tightening, he demands. "What’s inside the syringe?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>“There’s a researcher planning to do a mess up experiment! Let me explain…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>After listening to your explanation, the officer takes the syringe from you. “Thank you for informing me about this. We'll handle it from here.” He states. With that, you see the officer mutter something in his radio before running off to somewhere.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>Bump into the officer and inject them with the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>Just as you’re about to pass by, you stumble slightly and intentionally collide with the officer. In that fleeting moment of contact, you deftly press the syringe through the fabric of his uniform and inject the purplish liquid into their thigh.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“Hey! Watch where you’re going!” The officer yells at you. He doesn't seem to notice what you have done since he is too focused on regaining their balance and brushing off the minor inconvenience.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>Apologize and leave quickly.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>You mutter an apology and continue walking. Your heart is pounding but you maintain an air of nonchalance since you have successfully administered the injection without arousing suspicion.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Take a peek behind you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>You see the officer dusting off his uniform and preparing to walk away. However, he begins to stagger forward while his limbs twitch in an irregular manner. Eventually you see a stinger-like appendage burst out of his mouth as his body collapses to the floor and spasms violently.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>You see the officer dusting off his uniform and preparing to walk away. However, he begins to stagger forward while his limbs twitch in an irregular manner. To your horror, you suddenly see a stinger-like appendage burst out of his mouth as his body collapses to the floor and begins to spasm. Realization dawns on you as you understand the true nature of the syringe.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>However, the officer feels the sharp prick of the syringe piercing through the fabric of his uniform. His eyes widen in surprise as he quickly looks down, noticing the syringe sticking out of his thigh.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>"What the—?" He exclaims, yanking the syringe out and glaring at you with suspicion and anger. "What did you just inject me with?"</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>“Um… I can explain… It’s an enhancement drug.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>“As if I would believe that. Now you’re under arrest for commiting a crime!” He pulls out his baton but before he can lay his hands on you, you notice him stumble and his limbs twitching in an irregular manner. You watch in horror as a stinger-like appendage bursts out of his mouth. Eventually he collapses to the floor as his body begins to spasm.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2>Run away from the officer.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.c1>The officer grabs you by your shirt and pulls you back with great strength. “Nuh uh, you’re not going anywhere. You’re under arrest.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o1>Struggle to break free.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>Somehow you easily break free from his firm grasp. Finding it odd, you glance over to the officer, only to notice him stumbling while his limbs twitch in an irregular manner. You watch in horror as a stinger-like appendage bursts out of his mouth. Eventually he collapses in front of you as his body begins to spasm out.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o2>Punch the officer.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o2.c1>The officer loses his grip as staggers backwards the moment your fist connects to his face. When he tries to reach for you again, you notice his limbs start to twitch in an irregular manner. You watch in horror as a stinger-like appendage bursts out of his mouth. Eventually he collapses in front of you as his body begins to spasm out.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>“No, I’m not doing it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.c2>You take a closer look at the syringe, you can’t recognise the content inside.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2>“What’s inside the syringe?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.c1>“A formula I developed during my research, it’s supposed to enhance one’s physical capabilities.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1>“And you want me to try it?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“No. Unless you want to…” He speaks hesitantly, looking up and down on your body physique before shaking his head.  “Nah… I need a more healthy subject. Someone trained in a military field… Like that person.” He points towards a security officer at a distance.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“Why not test it on yourself?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Why would I do that?” He inquires, tilting his head slightly as if your question piques his interests.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“So that you will be able to know and understand how the drug works.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“That’s not a bad idea. If I inject myself, I can document the effects firsthand...” He remarks, taking out his notebook and pen as he prepares himself. "I'm sure I perfected the formula..." He mutters, removing the needle cap and injecting the purple liquid into his vein.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>A minute passes and nothing seems to happen. “Huh… No immediate adverse effects… No numbness to my limbs… I feel perfectly fin–” Before he can finish his sentence, you see him staggering.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He tries to say a word but his body starts twitching erratically and his limbs twist in unnatural directions. Next thing you know, a stinger-like appendage bursts from his mouth as he collapses and begins to spasm.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Leave quickly.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>“That sounds illogical, I need to be coherent to document the results accurately. Furthermore, if there are adverse effects and I die, who will continue the research?" The researcher remarks in a rather analytic tone.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“You’re right. So, what do I get in return for helping you?</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“So that you can get the taste of what you created.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2>“What do I get for helping you?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>“How am I going to ask that person to try the drug?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>"That’s for you to figure out." He replies frankly.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1>“Alright, I'll see what I can do.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2>“Nope, I'm not doing this.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.c3>You spot a middle-aged person in a lab coat pacing back and forth in annoyance. Occasionally muttering to himself about something as though he is cursing something or someone.</EventText.frenseynomor.c3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3>Approach the man.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.c2>Not bothering to look behind him, the researcher asks in a rather rude way, “Here to take more of my things huh?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o2>“Uh… Yes, I am here to rob you.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o2.c1>“Tsk… You already took everything. So, kindly shove your baton up your ass and screw off, would you?” He scoffs at your remark.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3>“No…? Why would I do that?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.c1>He finally turns to take a glance at you. “Oh! My apologies! I thought you were one of those guards patrolling the outpost…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1>“Did something happen?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.c1>“Yes. You see, I am a researcher myself and I study many fascinating creatures… However, the security guards recently confiscated my notes, and now I can't continue my research." He explains, pondering a solution to his predicament.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.c1>Suddenly his eyes sparkle as he asks, “Mayhaps you can help me get my stuff back?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1>“How can I help?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Since they don't recognize you, you can sneak into the office where they store confiscated items and retrieve the documents for me.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Wouldn’t that get me into trouble?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You're right... But I can create a distraction for the guards. That should give you enough time to retrieve my notes. How does that sound?” He replies.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Alright… Sounds simple enough.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Excellent! I'll go and distract the guard. Do make haste in retrieving my notes.” He comments.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>As the researcher goes to distract the guard, you head toward the office where confiscated items are kept. After searching around, you finally locate a metal crate labeled "Papers to burn."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Search the crate.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>It takes you a few minutes to sift through the pile of documents. Eventually you find a file containing the researcher’s notes.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Read the notes.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The notes contain detailed information about husk anatomy and their functions, including test results conducted on some husk crawlers. Yet something catches your attention, “...Is it possible to harness the genetics of the husk to aid human evolution? To achieve perfect symbiosis? … If only I had time to put the drug to the test…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Search the other crates for more items.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Leave the office.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>Despite the heated conversation between the guard and the researcher, you quickly open a nearby crate and find a few seized goodies inside.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Take a few vials of unknown substances.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>You take a few vials of drugs from the crate and quickly leave the office before the guards notice you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Finally, it took you 10 years to get here! Now I know it’s not my position to ask but was it really necessary to steal other items?” He asks out of curiosity.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>"Yes."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>He sighs, “I guess it is not my position to question your ethics. Anyway, are you able to find my documents?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>Pass the documents to the researcher.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>He grabs them eagerly and checks it. Afterwards a smile appears on his face, “Thank you… Now that the troublesome bit is over, I can continue my research. Here, take this for your troubles.” He takes something from his pocket and hands it to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Take it.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Now time is of the essence, I must head back to my research lab.” He declares and scurry off to somewhere else.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>"No."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>He stares at you dumbfounded, “No? Was what you did simply for fun or something?” He pauses and pinches the bridge of his nose. Then he continues, “Nevermind, don’t answer that. It’s irrelevant to the subject at hand. Did you manage to find my documents?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>“Finally, it took you 10 years to get here! Did you manage to retrieve the documents?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>“Not yet.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>“Then what are you doing here? Go get them!" He exclaims.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>Take a handgun.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>You take an odd-looking pistol from the crate and quickly exit the office before the guards notice you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>You grab a revolver from the crate and quickly exit the office before the guards notice you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3>Take an explosive bomb.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3.c1>You grab a homemade dirty bomb from the crate and promptly leave the office before the guards notice you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3.c2>You grab a homemade compound N from the crate and promptly leave the office before the guards notice you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o3.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>You glance at the two men conversing and notice the guard occasionally looking your way. However, the guard's attention quickly returns to the researcher who is causing a scene. You realize it is best if you leave now before the guard comes to you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Sorry, I won't do it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He sighs in resignation, “What a pity… Now excuse me, I do not have time to linger and chat, I must retrieve my research documents before the guards burn them.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Sure… I can do that for you.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Excellent! I'll await your return with my documents.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>When no one is looking, you slip into the office and find a metal crate labeled “Papers to burn.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>Before you can read the research note, you suddenly hear heavy footsteps advancing towards you as a guard shouts out, “Hey! You there! What are you doing here?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Uhm… I got lost and I’m looking for my friend.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I’m here to inspect the confiscated goods and make sure everything is in check.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>“Someone informed me that the lights were broken, so I came to fix it.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>Despite hearing some voices at the distance, you quickly open a nearby crate and see a couple of seized goodies in it</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>“You’re finally back. Did you manage to retrieve the documents?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>"Not yet."</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c3>Before you can do anything else, you suddenly hear heavy footsteps advancing towards you as a guard shouts out, “Hey! You there! What are you doing here?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>“Oh… I doubt your friend is here unless they are a security officer. Anyway, I suggest you leave and search elsewhere like the crew quarters or cafeteria.” The guard asserts while gesturing you to leave.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>Leave before the guard spots something is off.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c2>“Is that so?” The guard eyes you carefully before he chuckles, “You think I will believe that you conveniently stumble your way here to find someone?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o2>“Look, how about you turn a blind eye and let me go?”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c3>“Damn it, everything is fine. Tell the chief to stop sending people over to check on us.” The guard curses.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o3>Nod your head and leave before the guard spots something is off.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o3>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c4>“Really? Isn’t it weird to send a civilian over to do an inspection? Are you sure you’re not stealing something?” The guard eyes you carefully.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c4>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c5>“Right… Next time fix it when one of us is here. We don’t want any misunderstanding to occur.” The guard asserts while gesturing you to leave.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c5>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c6>“Really now?” The guard eyes you carefully before he says, “The lights have been fine this whole time… I smell someone is lying here.”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.c6>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.c1>“If someone here pays me 250mks, then perhaps I can close my eyes and pretend I saw nothing.” The guard gives you a cunning smile.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1>Pay 250mks to the guard.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.c1>He happily takes the money from your hands and a smirk appears on his face, “Ah yes, I definitely saw nothing. Must have been the wind I must say…”</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.c1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.o1>Leave before the guard changes his mind.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.o1>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.c2>“No money eh? No problem… I’ll just detain you and send you to jail.” The guard remarks, pulling out his baton and prepares to arrest you.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.c2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.o2>Time to run.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o1.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o2>Body slam the guard and run for it.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o2>
  <EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o2.c1>You slam into the guard with all your strength, knocking him to the floor. This gives you some time to escape as the guard struggles to regain his bearings.</EventText.frenseynomor.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o4.o4.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.c1>You decided to use the radio Kumo gave you and call her to see if she would answer. It did not take long before you heard a familiar voice answering the call. “Affirmative. This is Captain Kumo of the Separatists Vessel “Seawolf”. State your business.”</EventText.callingkumo.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1>Tell her your name.</EventText.callingkumo.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.c1>“Ah… I was wondering when you would be calling. I assume you called to collect the favor I owe?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1>“Yes.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.c1>“Right, to business then. As promised, I will give you anything as long as it is in my capability to acquire them. What is it that you want?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1>“Money. I’m low on cash.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.c1>“That’s not an issue for me. I can transfer over 3,500mks to your wallet.” </EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Sounds good.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I am sending the money over. Check and see if you receive it.” </EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Received.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Alright, now that everything is settled, as much as I like to keep in touch with you, it’s time for us to part ways. I rather not have any issues resurfacing from this incident and cutting contact is the best for all of us.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Farewell my friend. Oh and one more thing, the radio will self-destruct. I do suggest dropping.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Goodbye, Kumo. Wait what?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Come on, after all the effort I went through for you? You can at least give me more than that.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Hm… I can understand the troubles you had to go through to help me… Very well, I’ll give you 4,000mks instead. Check and see if you receive it.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>“I believe I am already quite generous with what I offer. I will not give anything more than that. Now check and see if you receive it.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2>“Guns. Lots of guns.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Guns eh? Sure. I’ll offer you 3 courses and in each course, choose the weapons that best suits you.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“For the appetizer, we have 2 sets of revolver armed with depleted fuel rounds capable of irradiating your targets. If you need a gun with a rapid fire rate, we have a SMG with both normal and depleted fuel magazines. Or maybe you prefer something that gives a punch? Like a riot shotgun loaded with 12 gauge shells?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“I’ll take the revolvers.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Good choice. Onwards to the main course… We have an assault rifle made by the Separatists with each magazine containing 30 rounds, good for raiding outposts as long as you can handle the weapon. If you want something robust, an auto shotgun pack with explosive slugs might be up to your taste. Or maybe you want something impactful? Like a grenade launcher with 40mm grenades?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“I’ll take the assault rifle.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“And lastly, the dessert… We have the classic boarding axe, able to deal devastating strikes against armored creatures and walls. Or if you want something small and swift, may I suggest a dementonite knife. This knife is infused with the alien materials called dementonite clusters. It’s very quick, deadly and tends to drive your opponent insane. "</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"If you don’t like that, I could also offer the europan handshake. Coated with morbusine poison, a few stabs with this knife will leave your enemy poisoned and gasping for air.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I’ll take the boarding axe.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Consider it done. I have sent the orders to the outpost manager. Head to the administrator room and talk to the person in-charge, they will pass you the weapons.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Noted."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Hey you! You must be the crew Kumo mentioned about... She said you ordered some weapons. They're in the duffle bags, so be sure to take them!"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh! I almost forgot! Here’s the melee weapon you requested too!”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Thanks."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I’ll take the dementonite knife.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>“I’ll take the europan handshake.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“I’ll take the auto shotgun.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>“I’ll take the grenade launcher.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4>“Come on, where are the big guns? Surely you can offer them to me…”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.c1>“You mean a high caliber machine gun capable of firing 100 bullets in 12 seconds? Hm… I can certainly get that weapon for you if you really want it.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o1>“I’ll take the HMG.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.c2>“Not sure what you are talking about… And even if I do, I wouldn’t offer such a deadly weapon to anyone.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.c2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o2>“Fine, I’ll take the assault rifle.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o3>“Fine, I’ll take the auto shotgun.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o4>“Fine, I’ll take the grenade launcher.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o4.o4>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2>“I’ll take the SMG.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o3>“I’ll take the riot shotgun.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o2.o1.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3>“Manpower. I need more crewmates.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.c1>"I should be able to recruit two seamen to your crew. Tell me, for your first crewmate, what types of personnel are you looking for?"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1>"Captain."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>"And your second crewmate?"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>"Consider it done. I have sent the necessary documents to the HR department, they will be sending two new members to your crew. Do expect to see them soon."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Farewell my friend and have a safe trip. Oh and one more thing, the radio will self-destruct. I do suggest dropping.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>"Security Officer."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>"Medical Doctor."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3>Next.</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o1>"Engineer."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o2>"Mechanic."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o3>"Assistant."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o4>Back.</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o3.o1.o3.o4>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4>“You. I want you on my crew.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.c1>She chuckles, “A little too late for that, don’t you think? I’ve already submitted the documents to take over this crew, I can’t leave them now since I am the captain of my ship. However, I can help you recruit two crewmates if you are in desperate need of helping hands.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o1>“No, I need money.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o2>“No, I want guns.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o3>“Yes, I like to have more crewmates.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o3.c1>"Okay. So tell me, for your first crewmate, what types of personnel are you looking for?"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o1.o4.o3.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2>“No.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.c1>“Huh? Then what is the purpose of this call?” She asks, a little bewilder by your action.</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1>“I thought we could have a conversation.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.c1>“A conversation? Aren’t you an amusing one? I guess I do not mind having a talk… What is it that you like to ask?”
</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1>“How have you been faring?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Well… With my new promotion as a captain and the death of my old captain, I am definitely doing a lot better. Thank you for asking.” She replies casually.</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Look, I know Captain Smith wasn’t a traitor. Tell me… Why did you want him dead?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“Do you have any interesting stories throughout your travels?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>“Well… Since you found out the truth, I guess there is no need for me to hide it anymore. There are two reasons why I wanted him dead. One was because he always placed his crewmates in danger. To him, the lives of a few people were nothing compared to his own quest for power and knowledge.”
</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>“And the second reason?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>“The second reason was because I wanted my revenge on him for killing my former captain… For killing someone who raised me when I was young… Someone who I saw as a fatherly figure.”
</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1>“I can understand your actions.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“I’ll be honest, I didn’t expect you to understand my situation. That said, I’m truly grateful for your help. If you hadn’t taken the job, I would still be stuck here dealing with that bastard. So whatever you need, I’ll do my best to help you get it."</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Let’s get back to business.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2>“It still doesn’t feel right to kill someone for the sake of avenging someone else…”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>“I don’t expect you to understand, you’ve probably never lost someone close to you to truly know how it feels. Regardless, I appreciate your help in taking that bastard down. Whatever you need, I’ll help you get it. I don’t like leaving debts unpaid.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.c2>“A conversation? Aren’t you an amusing one? I guess I do not mind having a talk… What is it that you like to ask?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.c2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2>“Tell me, how did you find out that your captain was a traitor?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c2>“I have my own ways of finding out the truth… Plus being the second in command, you would have to follow him around and obey his orders. Eventually he lets his guard down and you’ll see his true colors.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c3>“Hm… I do have a tale or two worth sharing. Especially this one, what started as a routine escort mission quickly turned into chaos. Out of nowhere, a Coalition submarine ambushed us. Somehow, they managed to board our sub and I was among the first to confront the attack. I took down a few Coalition soldiers before they overpowered me. In the end, I was captured by the Coalition.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.c3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3>“What happened afterwards?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.c1>“I was brought in and forced to stand in front of the Coalition council… I must say, it felt like I was being watched by a pack of hungry mudraptors. They demanded my execution but I managed to negotiate for my life. In exchange for my freedom, I had to share valuable information about the Separatists. Of course, I only gave up non-essential details. That was enough to satisfy them and they released me… Under the condition that I serve aboard a Coalition submarine called Sorrowful.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1>“How was it like working in a Coalition submarine?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.c1>“It was horrible. The captain did not care for his crew and was fixated on following the Coalition laws. Breaking even a minor rule meant facing death or something worse.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.c1>“I remember there was this mechanic… I believe his name was Shepard… He got caught stealing from an outpost. When the captain found that out, he literally ordered one of the doctors to amputate mechanic’s hand as punishment. Afterwards, the poor guy ended up going crazy from the pain and trauma.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You think this would intimidate people from trying to do crime. Which it did work on his crew but it didn’t work on me. For someone who is an expert at stealing, I know my ways around thievery. Hell, I even stole a few bottles of expensive booze from the captain himself! The captain spent weeks hunting for the culprit but never found a trace haha.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Nice. How about security?"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“They were god damn incompetent. There was this one incident, I was in the reactor room when a mudraptor broke in. I fled towards the nearest room for safety and the moment I opened the door, a security officer shot off my right leg!”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I shit you not, I instantly fell onto the floor and I didn’t even realize my leg was gone until a medic pointed it out. I was then dragged to medbay to get treated… I could barely remember the rest as I slipped in and out of consciousness from all the blood loss.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Now that I think about it, I wasn’t really lucky when I was with that crew. I was in so many accidents that I lost count… I actually felt bad for the medics, they had to patch me up every single time. In fact, I even got to know one of the medics personally. Her name was Dr. Pierce… She had a cold demeanor but always treated me nicely.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Even when she found out I was once a Separatist, she never really held hostility towards me. I kind of wish I could meet her again or if I could, I like to bring her over towards the Separatists. At last, it’s a shame we stand on different sides and I bet it’s best if I don’t find her…”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Dr. Pierce… You mean Bridgette Pierce?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Wait… Do you know her? Have you met her before?” She asks in surprise.</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“No, I heard it from a commissar who used to work in that crew.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Tell me, did that commissar mentioned anything about her?”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Yes, she mentioned that Pierce took over as captain after the previous one went missing.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“She is the captain now? That’s... Unexpected.” Her voice trails off and she mutters something under her breath, barely audible but you manage to catch it through the radio, “Maybe I should find her again.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Kumo?"</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She clears her throat, snapping back to the moment. “Thank you for the information. Anyway, that’s enough chit chat for now. Let’s get back to what you came here for.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I agree.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No, I want to hear more stories.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“I would love to share more but I have matters to attend to. So sadly I can’t keep this up.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Aww…”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No, that’s all I know.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Oh… That’s disappointing… Anyway, that’s enough chit chat for now. Let’s get back to what you came here for.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Haha. Look at me, rambling on and on about the past... It’s best if I stop and get back to what you came here for.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o1.o2.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o2>“I’m joking, I am here to collect what was owed.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o2.c1>" As much as I love the silliness, I would rather we not waste anymore time.”</EventText.callingkumo.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.c1>You see a high ranking officer in formal attire befitting a First Mate leaning against a wall. Her furtive eyes glance through the passersby until her eyes meet yours. She pushes herself off the wall and slowly approaches you, a friendly smile can be seen on her face as she says, “Look who we have here… The new Underdog of the Jovian people…”</EventText.kazuyakumo.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1>“Who are you?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.c1>“That’s not important right now, I’ve been looking for someone… And you look like the perfect person for the task. Interested in a job?” She asks.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1>“What’s the job?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.c1>She glances around her for a second, making sure no one is listening in on the conversation, before leaning closer to you to continue. “There’s a Coalition traitor among my crew and I need an outsider like you to get rid of him.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1>“Who is the traitor?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.c1>Her face seems to darken when she answers, “As much as I hate to say this, the traitor is my captain.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What?! If the captain is the traitor, why didn’t you report him to the authorities?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I can’t do that. Being the second in command, my movements are being watched by the captain. If I report to the authorities, I would be executed the moment my captain realizes what I did.” She responds calmly.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“So what do you suggest?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Kill the captain for me.” She asserts.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“No, I’ll be the witness and testimony to your actions. With that, you’ll be crowned as a hero among the Separatists… While I get to keep my crew safe.” A charming smile can be seen on the officer as the words leave her mouth.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What else would I get in return?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She ponders for a bit, before replying, “I could lend you a hand on your travels by joining your crew. After all, I am one with many talents and skilled in many aspects. Unless you prefer something else in return, I can arrange that too.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Then what would happen to your crew if you joined me?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I’ll make sure the crew gets a better captain once I leave them to join you.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Alright, I’ll help you with this. Give me a description of your captain.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No way I’m doing this, you’re on your own.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“His name is John Smith. He has a burn scar on his face and a security officer following him around like a dog. It’s not hard to miss.” She explains.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“I’ll see what I can do about your traitor incident.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“I’ll be waiting here for your good news and accomplishment.” She comments while giving a dry smile towards you.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>A scarred-faced captain and his commissar walk down the hallway. The numerous medals on the captain’s uniform indicate his prestigious status. He certainly matches the description of the traitor you’re looking for. You have the option to kill him now but perhaps talking to him first might reveal more about himself?</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Go through with the plan and kill him.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>A traitor is a traitor… There is no point chatting with them. The captain and his commissar notice your hostility and prepare to defend themselves.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>Fight.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The captain is dead and so is his loyal commissar. You should probably inform the first mate about your success...</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Haha! You have done well! News of the incident has spread quickly around the outpost. Don’t worry, I can handle any issues that arise from this. You have my words, you won’t get into any trouble.” She reassures you with a beaming smile.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I’m glad I could help but let’s talk about my reward.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Straight to the point? That’s fine by me. Still, where are my manners? My name is Kazuya Kumo, First Mate to the Separatists Vessel called Seawolf. Now have you considered my offer that I proposed earlier?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I did, welcome on board.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Thank you. Now that’s settled, I will join you as soon as you depart from the outpost. I just need to file some documents to the higher-ups and take care of a few loose ends here.” She says as she begins to leave.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Hold up, I like to ask you a few questions.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She turns to you as she lets out a sigh, “Like right now? Alright… Go on, what would you like to ask?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What was your crew tasked with?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“My crew is in charge of researching various artifacts and creatures in Europa.” She replies half heartedly to your question.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What types of artifacts have you found?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She chuckles, her tone playfully evasive. “Oh come now, I can’t just go around sharing what I have found… After all, it’s classified information.” Her teasing smirk lingers before softening into a sly smile. “But since we are going to be working together, I suppose I could share a little. My crew has been studying a material called dementonite that was extracted from an alien artifact. Have you heard about it?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Good, then you should have heard about its unnatural properties… How it makes someone see things that defy logic. I have been trying to find a way to use them and by sheer luck I manage to learn how to merge the materials with our everyday tools. And mind you, it wasn’t an easy task.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Does that mean you can craft me some dementonite tools?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“As long as you get me the materials and tools to craft them, I can certainly do it. But I must warn you that wielding such tools may drive you crazy…. And if that happens, don’t hold me accountable for it.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I know Captain Smith wasn’t a traitor. Tell me… Why did you want him dead?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Initially surprised, she quickly covers it with a soft chuckle. “Since you know the truth, I suppose I don’t need to pretend in front of you.” She raises 2 fingers and continues, “There are two reasons why I wanted him dead. One was because he always placed his crewmates in danger. To him, the lives of a few people were insignificant compared to his own quest for power and knowledge.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“The second reason is that I wanted my revenge on him for killing my former captain… For killing someone who raised me when I was young… Someone who I saw as a fatherly figure.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“And you think killing him would fix everything?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“No… It wouldn’t have brought back those who died… But at least I avenged their death and those who have suffered under his wraith.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“So what’s your side of the story?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“What do you mean by that?” She asks, a little confused by your question.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“How did you end up with the Separatists?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“It’s a long story but to keep it short, when I was a kid, a war broke out at the outpost where I lived. My parents were caught in the crossfire and died. Amidst all the chaos, a Separatist captain came and saved me. That’s how I found myself with them.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“How did you end up becoming a first mate of your crew?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“It’s a long story but to keep it short, I was forced to be a first mate by John Smith. Honestly, I didn’t want the position but he insisted that I take it. Rejecting it was never an option since he had me at gunpoint.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Why did he want you as his first mate?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“I don’t know, I never bother asking him. But from my guess, he either likes my talents or he just loves torturing me for whatever sick reason.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Alright, that's enough questions for now.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Wouldn’t it be better to put him in jail?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“With his status and position, no. Believe me, I have tried but the evidence I once had is now deep in the abyss, making it impossible for me to throw him in jail.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Finally… I’ll go take care of things. I’ll see you later on.” She says, giving you a casual wave before walking away.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“No. What is it about?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Well… How do I describe it… Uh… It is something that exists beyond the realm of understanding… Even I have trouble comprehending it.” Her voice faltered, trailing off as though lost in a memory.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>For a moment, she blankly stares off into the distance with her furrow brows, before snapping out of the trance and rubbing the back of her neck with her hand. “Its shape and properties… Just feels unnatural. It’s hard to explain. Anyway, I have been trying to find a way to use them and by sheer luck I manage to learn how to merge the materials with our everyday tools. And mind you, it wasn’t an easy task.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“What creatures are you researching about?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Oh come now, I can’t just go around sharing what I have done… After all, it’s classified information.” She says in a teasing manner, before continuing with a sly smile. “But since we are going to be working together, I could share some details. My crew has been studying mudraptors and have been finding ways to tame them. During our research, we managed to encounter a rare type of mudraptor… A ruby raptor.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“What does it look like?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“It is basically a mudraptor with a reddish shell, almost pinkish in color. We tried to capture it once but that thing was as fast as a tiger thresher. After it got away, we never saw it again. I can’t help but wonder how rare it was... Probably could have fetched a hefty price if we managed to catch it.” She comments, her tone tinged with disappointment at the end.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“How did you find out that your captain was a traitor?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She gives you a smirk as she says, “I have my ways of finding out the truth… Plus being the second in command, you would have to follow him around and obey his orders. Eventually he lets his guard down and you’ll see his true colors.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I don’t need another crewmate… I want something else in return.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>One of her eyebrows rises at your statement. “Oh? I wasn’t expecting you to reject my proposal… But that’s fine.” She comments, raising her right hand to rub her chin thoughtfully.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>Eventually she reaches onto her belt, grabbing something and handing it to you. She continues, “To be honest, I don’t have much to offer at the moment… So tell you what, I’ll give you my radio. The frequency is already set, so you won’t need to remember it. When the time comes where you need help, just dock at a Separatists station and call me, I will return the favor."</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“How can I trust you won’t bail on me?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“If you are that paranoid, you can try calling me right now with the radio.” She replies calmly.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Try calling her on the radio.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>You press the button and speak into the radio. You can hear your own voice come through on the First Mate's radio, proving that it works. She smirks and says, “I assure you, I don’t hand out fake radios to someone who’s done me a great favor. Now does this ease your worries?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Alright, I’ll keep that in mind.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“You better keep your promise.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“It’s fine. I’ll trust you on this.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>“Now I shall get going, I got reports to do and things to clean up…” She says with a warm smile, giving you a casual wave before leaving.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c2>“I will. After all, I don’t like owing people a favor. Now if you’ll excuse me, I got reports to do and a mess to clean up.” With that, she leaves you to take care of her tasks.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>Approach the captain.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>The menacing captain notices you approaching and he questions, “Is there something you need, citizen?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Hey! It’s an honor to meet a captain like yourself! Can you please tell me some of your stories?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>The captain examines you carefully to find out your motive but the moment he sees your enthusiasm, he perceives you as another curious seaman. His demeanor changes to one that is prideful as he speaks arrogantly, “Ah… Another young seafarer with such curiosity. You’re lucky to meet someone like me, not many captains have time to chat. Very well, I’ll share some war stories from my time.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>You listen attentively as the captain points to each of his medals, explaining their significance. Some medals represent his brave conquests against various coalition outposts, while others commemorate his solo destruction of a fleet of coalition submarines. His feats are indeed remarkable. However, you suddenly grow curious about the burnt scars on his face.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“How did you get your scars?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“During an escort mission, I was ambushed by a coalition submarine. Those coalition scums boarded our submarine and attempted to capture my crew alive. I wasn’t going to let that happen, so I blew my submarine up, taking all those scums down with me. Somehow I survived the blast, I was stuck under some rumbles and a submarine dropped by to rescue me. That’s how I got my scars.” He answers.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“You killed your whole crew just to stop the Coalitions?!”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Of course. I did what was necessary to prevent valuable information from falling into our enemies’ hands. A death of a mere crew is nothing compared to the information we hold.” The captain states this coldly, as if it's a simple fact.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>After listening to the captain’s words, you realize he is not a traitor but a ruthless captain loyal to the Separatists. You wonder why his first mate wants him dead until it dawns on you that maybe she just wants to protect her crew from a captain that merely sees them as pawns to use and dispose off. Now you have to decide… To continue with the plan of murdering him, despite knowing he is loyal to the Separatists… Or betray the First Mate by revealing her assassination plans to gain favor with the merciless captain?</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Kill the heartless captain and his commissar.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>You prepare yourself to murder them. The surprised party has no choice but to defend themselves.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Betray the First Mate by revealing her assassination plans.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>The captain is not surprised by your revelation. He is well aware that such actions will happen eventually. Nonetheless, he thanks you for the information and rewards you with some cash before leaving to confront his first mate.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>You stumble onto a scene that looks like two high ranking officers having a serious conversation.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Damn those rats…” The first mate curses.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>The scarred-face captain stands tall, approaching his first mate with a sinister grin. He mocks her, “Kumo Kumo Kumo… You think you can outsmart me? Haven’t you learned from your mistakes? Now, I’m in a rather pleasant mood today… All you have to do is bow down and I’ll let it slide.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The first mate clutches her fists and her spiteful eyes lock onto her captain. “Oh fuck you, Smith. I am done being your tool for your selfish gains. This ends here!” Her angry voice echoes through the halls as she quickly draws her weapon to attack her captain.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Better leave while you can.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You god damn snitch! Get the hell out of my sight! I already have enough problems to deal with because of you.” She growls at you.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Once again, thank you for informing me about this. A shame such a potential person wasted her life for something so petty." The captain remarks.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>“What a shame… Here I thought you were the chosen one. I guess you aren’t what the people claimed you to be.” She remarks in a disappointing tone and begins to walk away from you.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o2>“If there is a traitor, why didn’t you get rid of him yourself?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o2.c1>She frowns at your question, “It’s complicated… I would have already done it myself a long time ago if I could. However, the traitor in question is my captain.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o2>“I’m not interested.”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o2.c1>She shakes her head and scoffs, “I guess I’ve made a poor judgment on the person.” She proceeds to move away as though she is looking for another potential person. </EventText.kazuyakumo.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o2>“Do I know you?”</EventText.kazuyakumo.o2>
  <EventText.kazuyakumo.o2.c1>“No… But you look like someone who could get things done. Interested in a job?” She asks.</EventText.kazuyakumo.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.c1>You stumble upon a familiar looking red crate lying about on the floor.</EventText.jokster.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1>Approach and open it.</EventText.jokster.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.c1>You open the crate and a clown pops out of it. “Ah! Praise the Honkmother! My favorite traveler! It’s so good to see you again! I would have offered you a game but you came at an unfortunate time…” The clown says solemnly.</EventText.jokster.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1>“What happened?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.c1>“The outpost security took away my possessions and now I’m left with nothing but you, me and my crate!” He exclaims as he paces back and forth around his crate.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1>“Uhhh… Okay.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.c1>“They never understand the true joy in life! They are such a killjoy!” He comments and stops right in front of you. Staring directly at you, he continues, “But you… You understand the thrill of fun! You always come back for more… Or perhaps it’s fate that we always meet! Say, you own a submarine right? Can I tag along? I would love to join you on your travels!”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Sure.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown jumps forward and embraces you in a tight hug. He lifts you off your feet and spins you around before letting you back down. “Hahaha! We’re going to be the best of friends! I can already feel it!”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh wait! I forgot the most important thing… Introduction!” He jumps gracefully onto his crate and small pieces of confetti scatter around the air as he begins to introduce himself, “I am Jokster! A humble clown to our great Honkmother. And soon to be your new friend!”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Hold up my friend! Since we are going to be close buddies from now on… As a gesture of good will, I would like to give you a small gift! Now all you have to do is make a random noise and I’ll instantly figure out what you want!” He states merrily.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“OooowOowOweewehehe Quack Quack.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Quack quack? Oh! Quack quack!” The clown mutters to himself and immediately goes towards his red crate, pulling out a giant rubber ducky and places it into your hands. “Here’s your quack quack!” He mentions excitedly.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>...</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Noticing your confused look, he realizes something is off. “Ohhhhh! That’s what you mean! Wait a second, I got it right here!” He quickly sticks his head into his crate as if he was searching for something.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Eventually he pulls out a person in a rubber ducky diving suit and drops the body in front of you. “Tada! Your rubber ducky suit!” The clown gestures at it while smiling broadly.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Check on the person.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Whoever is inside the diving suit is still alive and breathing. However, she remains unresponsive when you attempt to wake her up.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>That’s concerning…</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh, don’t worry about the person inside the suit. She’s been like this for a while now.” He comments casually.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Okay…?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I hope you enjoy your gift! I put a lot of thoughts into them! Now let’s not dally around! We got a trip to travel!” He assures you to go back to your tasks.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“ShhhreemTingingHoohoo Knoh Knoh.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>The clown listens carefully and then he sticks his hand into his pocket, pulling out a bike horn and placing it into your hands. “Here’s your knoh knoh!” He comments excitedly.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>Noticing your expression, he realizes something is off. “Is this not it? Wait wait wait, I knew it!” He moves toward his red crate and begins frantically searching for something.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“No no no, this isn’t it!” The clown mutters to himself as he tosses a harmonica over his shoulder and towards you.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>Catch the instrument.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Not this one either.” He mumbles, tossing an accordion over his shoulder and towards your direction.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>Catch the other instrument.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“This one? No, it’s too big.” He murmurs as he somehow pulls out a guitar from the red crate and easily throws it over his head and towards your way.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Catch the incoming instrument.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Ah ha! Found you!” The clown pulls out a pair of cymbals from his crate and moves toward you. “Here is your item!” He comments excitedly and places the instrument onto your already full arms.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Thanks?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>“RatatatatatatataRatatataaa Click Click.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>“Click click huh?” The clown sticks his hand into his pants and pulls out a switch. Then he places the switch into your hand and comments excitedly, “Here’s your click click!”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>Noticing your expression, he realizes something is off. “Ohhh! That’s what you mean! Wait a second, I got it right here!” He quickly sticks his head into his crate as if he was searching for something.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>Eventually he pulls out a pair of machine pistols and hands it over to you. “Here’s your ratata! Ammo not included of course!” He winks at you childishly.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>“Okay…”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Well, ‘Jokster’, I have a few questions.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Oh? Questions for me? Hehe! Ask away, my curious friend!” He replies.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>“Why are you called Jokster?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>“You see, my father is a joker and my mother is a jester… That’s why I’m Jokster!” The clown proclaims.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>“What are you good at?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>“I bring jokes to you and I’m good at motivating the crew! If you need someone to clown around, I am the one you call to town!” He chuckles.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>“Who is the Honkmother?”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.c1>The clown gasps in shock at your question. “How could you not know her?! She is everything yet nothing. She’s the abyss that rides the fish! The lady that holds the world in her grasp yet tosses a pie at the glass! She’s the fun that flows through our veins and makes us glee in pain!”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1>"Huh?"</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>He sighs loudly as he continues, “It’s hard for me to explain if you can’t see the path of the bike horn. And if I were to explain fully, then the joke would simply fall flat you see.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Alright, I have nothing else to ask.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Come on, don’t be like that! Imagine the fun we could have! You, me and your crew in a baby submarine! The fun would be endless!” The clown comments in an attempt to persuade you.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Fine, you can join us.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>“No, we don’t need any more crewmates.”</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>His shoulder slums down in disappointment and responds in a gloomily tone, “Aw… But we had so much fun! Oh well… I will just continue my merry way.” With that, he begins to walk away in a rather sad yet dramatic way.</EventText.jokster.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o2>Walk away from it.</EventText.jokster.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o2.c1>You decide to leave the crate alone. As you walk away, you hear grumble noises coming from the crate.</EventText.jokster.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.c2>You stumble upon a rather familiar looking red crate lying about on the floor.</EventText.jokster.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.c1>You open the crate and a clown pops out of it. The clown does a bow and greets you warmly, “Hello traveler! I was not expecting to see you again! It’s nice to see you well and healthy.”</EventText.jokster.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1>“What are you doing here?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.c1>“I’m here on clown business, by the request of our great Honkmother… Say, since you are here, do you like to play another game?” He asks.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.c1>“Hehehe! Fantastic!” The clown replies excitedly as he shoves his hands into his pocket and pulls out a color pill in each of his hands. “On my left is a blue pill. On my right is a red pill. All you have to do is choose one and eat it!” He playfully smiles at you as he offers the pills to you once again.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1>“Can you give me a hint on which pill is good?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>“One does not share what the pill does, but does know it gives a buzz. You will never know what’s in the pills, for it may help or it may kill. Do not think and just eat, for they will taste ever so sweet.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>Take the blue pill and eat it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>You eat the pill and it leaves a weird yet sweet aftertaste in your mouth. It will take a while before the pill takes effect.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh? Haha! An excellent choice! Let’s hope the pill aids you in any jolly way possible! Now business calls and I must go. I hope we meet again, traveler!” The clown giggles and runs away before you can say anything.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>As you walk around the area, you feel as though something was wrong with your body. You couldn't exactly tell what's wrong but your vision begins to blur and you definitely feel sick. Whatever was in the pill might have poisoned you...</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Better find a doctor soon.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>As you walk around the place, you feel slightly rejuvenated and any injuries you sustain before begin to slowly heal. Whatever was in the pill has made you feel better.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Nice.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>As you go about doing your task, you swear you see something run past you. When you turn your head to check, there is nothing there. Are you imagining things? Who knows? Perhaps there was something wrong with the pill you ate a while back...</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>Maybe it's time to see a doctor.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c4>As you go about doing your tasks, you notice your reflexes are faster than usual. You feel like you can definitely get things done swiftly. Whatever was in the pill has boosted you up.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c4>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>Hell yeah!</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o4>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c5>As you go about doing your tasks, you begin to feel feverish and your muscles start to ache. Whatever was in the pill had given you a sore throat too.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c5>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c6>As you walk around the area, you accidentally stub your toe on a table but you don't feel any pain. You decide to pinch yourself hard on the arm to see if you feel anything and you realize you don’t really feel pain. At this point, you feel as though you can wrestle a mudraptor with your bare hands and win the fight. Whatever was in the pill has jack you up.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c6>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c7>As you walk around the area, you suddenly collapse to the floor. When you wake up, your head is spinning and your body feels cold. You also realize you are bleeding on your chest. You are unsure what causes the bleeding but you get a feeling that it has something to do with the pill you took a while back.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c7>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c8>As you walk around the place, you feel a sharp pain coming from your stomach and you begin to vomit at the side of the hallway. You wipe off the puke that is still on your mouth and pant slightly in discomfort. Whatever was in the pill made you feel extremely sick.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c8>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5>Maybe it’s time to see a doctor.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o5>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c9>As you go about doing your tasks, you notice you haven’t been breathing for a while… In fact, you feel like your skin has grown resistant to the atmospheric pressure. Whatever was in the pill has made you immune to pressure for the time being.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c9>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>Take the red pill and eat it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>As you go about doing your tasks, you start to feel feverish... As if your whole skin is burning. Perhaps the pill you ate contained something radioactive?</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>As you walk around the place, your body begins to feel stiff and your movement slowly becomes rigid. Whatever was in the pill might have caused this...</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c3>As you walk around the area, you suddenly clutch your chest tightly with your hands and begin gasping for air... Whatever was in the pill had certainly screwed you up...</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c4>As you go about doing your tasks, you suddenly lose consciousness and collapse on the floor. By the time you wake up, you feel like you just hit your head on something and you struggle to regain your footing as you feel disoriented. Whatever was in the pill has certainly given you a splitting headache.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c4>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c5>As you go about doing your tasks, you begin to feel an unbearable pain coming from your abdomen, as if something is burning through your stomach. Perhaps the pill you took from the clown was a bad choice...</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c5>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3>Observe the clown.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>You study the clown closely, he looks exactly like how he was when you first met him. However, when you take a closer look at his face, you notice that his red ball on his nose seems awfully shiny compared to the last time you met him. Perhaps you want to do something mischievous?</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>Honk the clown’s nose.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>You press hard on it and he flinches away from your hand, causing you to rip off his red nose. Placing his hands over his nose, he screams loudly as if he’s in pain, “AHHH! What have you done! It hurts!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>“Oh no…”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>Seeing your panic expression, his screaming turns into laughter as he removes his hands from his nose to laugh at you. You can see he is perfectly fine. In fact, there is a new red nose replacing the one you took. When you look at the fake nose that is in your hand, you notice there is a purple pill hidden inside it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Oh? How interesting… I was expecting you to take the purple pill… No matter, you still made a great choice. Let’s hope the pill aids you in any jolly way possible! Now business calls and I must go. I hope we meet again, traveler!” The clown giggles and runs away before you can say anything.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>Take the purple pill and eat it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>You eat the pill and oddly enough, it tastes extremely sweet when it touches your tongue. It will take a while before the pill takes effect.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Oh? What an interesting choice you made! Well done… Let’s hope the pill aids you in any jolly way possible! Now business calls and I must go. I hope we meet again, traveler!” The clown giggles and runs away before you can say anything.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>As you walk around the area, you suddenly feel as if your brain has expanded and you seem to be wiser than usual. Whatever was in the pill has made you more experienced than before.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>As you walk around the place, your eyes slowly widen as knowledge floods into your mind. You realize you know how to fabricate backpacks at the back of your head. You guess eating the purple pill was not a bad idea after all.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Cheers.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>As you go about doing your tasks, you suddenly feel a surge of energy. You are able to run faster, hit things harder and hold your breath longer than usual. Whatever was in the pill has temporarily made you a killing machine.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>“Haha, that’s funny.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2.c1>Eventually his screaming turns into laughter when he notices you laughing. He removes his hands from his nose and you can see he is perfectly fine. In fact, there is a new red nose replacing the one you took. When you look at the fake nose that is in your hand, you notice there is a purple pill hidden inside it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>You study the clown closely, he looks like any other clowns you have seen in Europa. Just a goofy innocent clown offering you rather peculiar pills.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2>Stare at the clown.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>The clown stares back at you with each colored pill on his hands, waiting for your decision.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1>Continue to stare at the clown.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.c1>The clown continues to stare back at you with each pill in his hands. He waits patiently for you to make a choice.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.c1>He gazes at you as you gaze back at him, his unwavering hands holding tightly onto the colorful capsules. He awaits your move.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown tilts his head slightly at your constant staring without moving the rest of his body. You swear you hear a crack from his neck. Yet the clown carries on with the stare without batting an eye.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown finally breaks eye contact, glancing between the two pills in his hands, he begins to juggle the pills. At some point, you notice that the two pills he was juggling turns into three… And then four… And five… As soon as he catches all of them, he extends one pill in each hand towards you. Somehow, the rest of the pills magically disappear into thin air like they were never there.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown pulls his pants outwards and drops the pills into his pants. Shaking his hips a little, he extends his hands out towards you again, offering the same coloured pills to you. You are left wondering how the pills end up in his hands…</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown pops the pills into his mouth and swallows them. Afterwards he tilts his head to the side and smacks his head a few times with his left hand, causing the pills to drop out of his ear and onto his hand. Then he proceeds to offer the pills to you and waits for you to make a decision.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown claps his hands together tightly and opens his palms. Instead of seeing the pills, you see a shimmering pile of purple dust leaving his hands as he shakes it off. He shoves his hands into his pockets, pulls out another set of pills and waits for you to decide.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown snorts the pills into his red nose and begins to wheeze a little. Eventually he coughs, spitting out the pills onto each of his hands and offers it to you.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clown tosses the pills over his shoulder and proceeds to pull out a scroll from his shirt. He carefully unrolls the scroll and starts to read it out loud to you, “Dear player… Will ye make a choice in choosing thy pills? For I will run out of words to write if thou keep this up. Yours sincerely, Noveva, the author of this event.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Once he finishes the wonderful speech, he pulls out the two pills from his pockets and waits for your response.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Heed the advice and eat the blue pill.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Heed the advice and eat the red pill.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>“Dammit, I thought this would work on you… Oh well, I guess you became a mute… Which isn’t a bad thing because if you make a sound now, I will literally explode and die! Hehehaha!” The clown proclaims.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>“Boo!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>“Noooo! You said a word! Now I’m going to–”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>Before the clown can finish his words, he explodes into a pool of crimson blood, leaving behind his clown shoes and money on where he stood. </EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>Pick up the free cash from the corpse and leave.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>You pick up 500mks from the bloody clown and quickly leave before anyone notices the incident.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>Without a warning, the clown shoves both the pills deep into your throat and shuts your mouth abruptly. You try to spit out the pills but you realize they are stuck and you end up coughing violently instead.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.c1>By the time you regain your footing, the clown is gone and you end up swallowing both the red and blue pill. Let’s hope they are nothing bad…</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1>Pray silently.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.c1>As you walk around the place, you suddenly feel a sharp pain in your chest like someone is breaking your ribs from the inside. The next thing you know, a baby mudraptor burst out of your chest and you are left horrified with what you see. You try to react but you immediately pass out from the shock.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>Eventually you wake up and remembering your situation, you try your best to defend yourself from the newborn creature. However, when you look around, it is nowhere in sight. Feeling confused, you check your chest. Instead of a big hole, you find out that there were deep cuts and scratches all over it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>You glance over at your hands and they are covered in blood. Did you cause this? Or was it the effects of the pills? Whatever it is, you need to find a doctor quickly before you bleed to death.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Help… Help me.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>While you desperately try to stop the bleeding, you feel as though your wounds begin to seal themselves and your bleeding slowly comes to a halt. Was it the effects of the pills again…?</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>I don’t know.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.c2>“Come on… You travel this far… Why not take a break and play a little game? Trust me, it will be fun!” The clown assures you innocently.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o2>“Fine, let’s play.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o3>“No, I’m leaving.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o3.c1>His shoulder slums down in defeat and responds in a gloomily tone, “Aw… What a party pooper you are!” He begins to walk away in a rather sad yet dramatic way.</EventText.jokster.o3.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.c2>You try to walk away from the crate but the lid of the crate pops open. A clown raises from it, stretches his arms up as he does a big yawn. He asks casually, “Who disturbs my slumber?” However, his sleepy demeanor changes to a lively mood when he sees you. “Oh! Hi there traveler! I was not expecting to see you here!”</EventText.jokster.o3.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.c3>You stumble upon a suspicious looking crate lying about on the floor.</EventText.jokster.c3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3>Approach the crate.</EventText.jokster.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.c3>As you move closer to it, you see a clown symbol on the crate. You wonder why there is a clown crate lying about in the middle of nowhere. Do you wish to open it?</EventText.jokster.o3.c3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o2>Check the crate by shaking it.</EventText.jokster.o3.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o2.c1>You attempt to pick up the crate to shake it but fail to do so as it seems to be quite heavy.</EventText.jokster.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o2.o1>Open the crate.</EventText.jokster.o3.o2.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o2.o2>Walk away from the crate.</EventText.jokster.o3.o2.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.c1>The moment you pry the lid open, a clown comes bursting out of the crate, sending the lid flying towards a random direction.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.c1>“My my! Who do we have here? Another traveler wandering amidst the land? Say, it has been a while since I saw your kind.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.c1>“A faithful disciple to our great Honkmother! Here to bring joy to all around!” The clown opens his hands out in a dramatic fashion.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1>“Why are you in a crate?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>“It’s my home of course! Very cozy and warm!” The clown says in a cheerful manner.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Okay, what do you want?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I want to play a game. And I’m sure you do too! So, let’s play a game!” He says gleefully.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Hahaha! I knew you would say yes!” The clown prances around for a while before stopping right in front of you. He shoves his hands into his pockets, pulling out a pill on each of his hands and extends them towards you. “On my left is a blue pill. On my right is a red pill. All you have to do is choose one and eat it! Simple yes?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What do the pills do?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“That won’t be fun if I tell you what it does… And the thrill is finding it out yourself!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Ohhh! Hehe… Good choice! Let’s hope the pill helps you in any funny way it can! Now I have to go… I hope we meet again, traveler!” The clown chortles and runs away before you can say anything.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Boo!"</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Before the clown can finish his words, he explodes into a pool of crimson blood, leaving behind his clown shoes and money on where he stood.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Help... Help me.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Nope.”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Come on, it will be a fun game! I promise! You can trust me, traveler!” The clown assures you.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>His shoulder slums down in defeat and responds in a gloomily tone, “Aw… I thought we could have fun! What a party pooper!” He begins to walk away in a rather sad yet dramatic way.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o2>“What are you doing in a crate?”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Working of course! Like how you work in a submarine, I have my own workplace too you know!” The clown exclaims.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1>Punch the clown in the face.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.c2>The clown winces in pain and clutches his red nose. Then he begins screaming at the top of his lungs. “Security! Security! There is a guy assaulting me! I need HELP!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3>Look around.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.c1>Regardless of how much the clown screams, the security personnels ignore the clown and continue their patrol like nothing happened.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1>Punch the clown in the face again.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>Another groan left the clown’s mouth. He rubs his face and his cheerful voice changes to a more threatening tone, “Don’t make me shit my pants!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>Punch the clown for the third time.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>This time the clown takes the punch straight on and his red nose dent inwards on his mask. He pulls up his long sleeves as if he was ready to give a fist fight but then he thinks for a second. Soon, he changes his mind and sticks his hand into his pants, pulling out a HMG. Pointing the gun at your face, he declares loudly, “I will defend myself!”</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>Oh no… Time to defend yourself!</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>Leave the bruised clown alone.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2.c1>That’s enough punching for the day. You left the bruised clown who is still trying to get the attention of the guards. </EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o2>Leave the clown.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>It’s best to get away before trouble comes. You left the screaming clown who is still trying to get the attention of the guards.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1.o1.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.c2>Before you can walk away, a clown comes bursting out of the crate, sending the lid flying towards you. You manage to duck under the lid before it hits your face.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.c2>
  <EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1>Phew... That was close.</EventText.jokster.o3.o3.o1>
  <EventText.jokster.o4>Leave it alone.</EventText.jokster.o4>
  <EventText.jokster.o4.c1>You decided to leave the crate alone. As you walked away, you swore you heard a chuckle coming from the crate.</EventText.jokster.o4.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.c1>You enter a scene where you witness a military officer engage in a tense confrontation with three civilians. Based on what you can see, you feel that something is about to happen.</EventText.sadashikira.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1>Watch from a distance.</EventText.sadashikira.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.c1>The officer maintains her stance, exuding authority as she addresses the group with confidence. However, you notice two individuals exhibiting defiance, while the last person appears nervously twiddling with something in their pocket.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1>Observe the two bold civilians.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.c1>They look like they do not want to cooperate with the officer… Not only that, they seem to be acting imprudent towards her.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.c1>Before she can utter another word, the two defiant civilians launch an attack on her, while the anxious civilian makes a dash to flee from the scene. "Stop that individual! He's carrying a bomb!" The officer shouts, attempting to alert her colleagues to the fleeing suspect.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1>Chase after the nervous civilian.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>As you close in on the civilian, he finds himself trapped and with no place for escape. Desperate, he turns toward you, attempting to draw a revolver from his pocket.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Stop! I want to talk!”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Talk?! Is that why you're chasing me?" The civilian queries, casting a puzzled glance your way, uncertain whether to initiate an attack or not.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Calm down, you don’t need to do this.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"I– I don't want to... They forced me into this. I have no choice, they'll kill me if I refuse!" He cries out, his hands shaking as he aims the gun at you.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Drop your weapon and surrender yourself. I’m sure they will lessen your crimes if you cooperate.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>After a moment of contemplation, he pleads in desperation, "Please, don't report me. I can't afford to be arrested! I'll drop the weapon and hand over the bomb. Just act like you never saw me and I'll disappear from your life."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Okay, hand over the items.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The civilian complies, surrendering both the gun and the device. "Thank you. I'll disappear before you know it." He says before bolting away at full speed.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>Fortunately, the bomb device is inactive. You should probably bring it back to the officer.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No, I can’t do that.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Then you leave me no choice…” He says with a somber expression, raising his gun toward you. With no alternative, you're forced to defend yourself.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>"No... The coalition won't show mercy. In their eyes, I'm already condemned. I– I'm sorry, but I had no other option." He says with a somber expression, raising his gun toward you. With no alternative, you're forced to defend yourself.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Attempt to disarm the person while they are distracted.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Attempt to disarm the person.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>You move swiftly, grabbing their wrists and dislodging the revolver from their grasp. The civilian is taken aback but quickly recovers and reaches for a knife, clearly intent on causing you harm. </EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>You retrieve the device from the civilian. Luckily, the bomb appears to be inactive. It would be wise to bring it back to the officer.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>You attempt to disarm the civilian, but he skillfully evades your grasp, keeping himself out of reach. Now, you find yourself staring down the barrel of a gun.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Oh no...</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>Rush the person.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>Upon seeing you approach, the civilian becomes frantic, causing him to falter in his movements and providing you with an opportunity to capitalize on the situation.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>When you return to the officer's side, you see she has successfully subdued the attackers. Now she is tending to her wounds while giving orders to the guards to begin patrols.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>Approach the officer.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>She shifts her focus to you as she notices you drawing near.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>Pass the bomb device to her.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She takes a moment to examine the device before remarking, “It’s not armed, that’s good. What happened to the culprit?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“He got away.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Interesting… How did you acquire the bomb?” She inquires.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>”He dropped it while running away.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I see…” She beckons one of the guards over and entrusts them with the device. After briefing them on what needs to be done, the guard nods and departs. Returning her focus to you, she adds, “I wasn't expecting to see you again but I am glad you are here. If you didn't intervene, the situation may have escalated.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Glad I could help, how have you been?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I’ve been good. Life is still the same for a soldier like me.” She answers briefly.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Continue."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She suddenly shifts the topic and says, “Although, there is a question I would like to ask you personally.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Okay.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“The first time we met, you said you were heading towards the Eye of Europa. What is your reason for going there?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I want to know what lies in the Eye of Europa.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I see…”  She murmurs, her fingers resting under her chin as she contemplates something.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Wait, why did you ask this question?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“To get away from jovian radiation.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“But isn’t heading deeper into the abyss dangerous as well? From what I know, the deeper you go, the more abyssal creatures you’ll meet.” She says.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“It is better than slowly dying to radiation.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>“Fair point.” She remarks at your statement.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“I’ve been thinking for a while now… About the Eye… I wish to visit it again and since your crew is heading there, I’m wondering if your crew is willing to accept another officer.” She asks.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Of course! We could use another person like you.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“By the way, I haven’t actually introduced myself. Name's Sadashi Kira, or you can call me Sergeant Kira.” She states, extending her hand out to shake yours.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Great! Welcome on board.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Wait, I have a request before I join. Is your crew able to provide alcohol for me throughout the journey?” She inquires.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Sure, we have alcohol on board, we can provide some for you.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>A faint smile tugged at her lips as she murmured, “Finally, I don’t need to be sober for this shit…” Upon catching your raised eyebrow, she hastily conceals her smile. “Ahem... I’ll report for duty once we depart from here. For now, I need to submit reports about this incident to the higher ups.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Sorry Sarge, we need you sober for this one.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>She lets out a disappointing sigh, “Understood. I’ll report for duty once we depart from here.  For now, I need to submit reports about this incident to the higher ups.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Hold up, can I ask you a few questions?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Affirmative. Ask away.” She replies.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“What do you specialize in?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>"I specialize in close-quarters combat." She declares, gesturing to the boarding axe strapped behind her back. "If any hostiles breach the submarine, I can handle them with ease. Additionally, if you need a gunner on the submarine, I can do that as well. So, feel free to assign me wherever needed."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“Why do I see you on different outposts?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“The coalition assigned me to do an inspection on their outposts. This is to ensure another incident like Sigil does not happen again.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Sigil incident?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Not sure if you were aware, but there was a husk outbreak during a ceremony in a city called Sigil. We had no clue how it happened but we lost over a hundred people to the husk parasite. Now that outpost is overrun with the husks and any attempt in reclaiming it is futile.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“That’s awful.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Yeah… And my previous crew was on that station when it happened. I should have interrogated the captain about the incident when I joined his crew. However, I think it doesn’t matter anymore at this point.” She added.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Why did you leave your previous crew?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“It’s a long story… If I start from the beginning, our captain was kidnapped by separatists on an outpost. I tried to reach him in time to save him but I was too late. Somehow they planned the ambush from the start, catching us off guard. In the end, the whole crew became a mess without a captain to lead the way.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Our Chief Medical Officer, Bridgette Pierce, ended up being the new captain for the crew. However, I believe she wasn’t mentally ready for the role. She did not have the skills to keep the crew together. So, I just couldn’t stay in a crew that is falling apart…”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Why didn’t you become the captain instead?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I did think about it… It probably would have been better if I was the captain…” She states solemnly as her eyes show a subtle glint of remorse. Soon, she composes herself and continues, “But I rather be at the front lines risking my life to protect my crew. After all, that’s what I was trained to do, to save people. Plus I don’t like the idea of sitting behind a navigation terminal while my comrades risk their life to protect me.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“Sorry, we have enough people at the moment.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Understood. Well… Once again, thanks for the help. I’ll have to return to my duty and file a report about this incident.” With that, she departs to resume her work.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>“I heard rumors that the Eye can stop the radiation, so I’m heading there to see if it’s true.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>“I don't know.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>She raises one of her eyebrows and asks, “If you're uncertain, why are you still heading in that direction?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>”Somehow I feel it calls for me… That I must reach it.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>“Hm… It looks like the Eye calls for those who seek it… Or more like sing for us to reach it.” She mutters as she places her fingers under her chin, pondering about something.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2>“There is nothing to do here, so I guess I yearn for adventure.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“Could have been better. I got into an incident a while back, someone knocked me out and stole my valuables… Not sure who it was but I’m sure it’s some lowlife.” She responds with a hint of disdain.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>"Oh... I wonder who would do that."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>She suddenly shifts the topic and says, “Anyway, there is a question I would like to ask you personally.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>“I’ve been good. In fact, I heard from my peers that someone from your crew rescued me when I was incapacitated by a separatist captain some time ago. Just letting you know, I appreciate that. If it weren't for your crew, I wouldn't be here today.” She answers with a hint of gratitude.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>"Your welcome."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I managed to snatch it off him while fighting him.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I dealt with him.”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>Toss the bomb device towards her.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>With effortless grace, she snags the device with a single hand and furrows her brow in slight concern. After inspecting the device, she remarks, “Not armed, good. You shouldn’t be tossing a device like that. Anyway, what happened to the culprit?”</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c2>When you return to the officer's side, you see she has successfully subdued the attackers. Now she is tending to her wounds while giving orders to the guards to begin patrols. It’s best not to disturb her unless you have the bomb to show as proof that you've dealt with the culprit.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2>Do nothing about it.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
An urgent announcement blares over the PA system. "Attention, everyone. We have reason to believe that a bomb has been planted on the station. Exercise caution and evacuate to a secure area immediately."</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>You found the bomb lying on the floor. There is no way to defuse it. Better find a way to get rid of it!</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>Shit...</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o2>Observe the nervous civilian.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o1.o2.c1>The civilian seems to be hiding something. From where you are standing, you can almost see a device with random wires sticking out of their pocket.</EventText.sadashikira.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o2>Move closer and listen in.</EventText.sadashikira.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o2.c1>As you draw nearer, you notice a flicker of recognition in the officer's eyes upon sensing your presence. However, she maintains a stern expression as her attention returns to the civilians. “I won't repeat myself. I'm here to conduct a search and it’s best if you cooperate.” She asserts firmly.</EventText.sadashikira.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o2.o1.c1>“You officers always love sticking your nose where they don't belong! To hell with this!” One of the civilians retorts, signaling to a nervous companion behind him, who stammers nervously, "W-Wait, now?"</EventText.sadashikira.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Yes! Do it!” He exclaims. With that, the nervous civilian takes off, brandishing a device adorned with an array of colored wires. You observe the officer attempting to pursue the fleeing individual, only to be intercepted by two burly civilians intent on assaulting her. "Damn it! Stop that guy! He got a bomb!" The officer shouts, attempting to capture her colleague's attention amidst the chaos.</EventText.sadashikira.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.c2>As you enter the room, your eyes are drawn to the weary figure before you, a military officer that you have met a while back. However, she looks different… Her uniform, once a symbol of discipline and authority, now hangs loosely from her frame, the fabric wrinkled and stained with the dust of neglect.</EventText.sadashikira.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.c1>You notice the telltale signs of exhaustion etched into every line of her face. No matter what the clowns do around her, her eyes seem unfocused as her gaze is fixed on a distant point… As if lost in a world of her own.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.c1>“I… I can’t take this anymore. This… This has to end.” She mumbles to herself, unaware of your presence.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1>“Hey, snap out of it!”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.c1>Your words fall on deaf ears as her hands reach over for her shotgun. She pulls the gun barrel towards her head, placing it right under her chin… Her index finger on the trigger.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1>“Wait, stop!”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clowns halt their movement as a heavy silence descends upon the room. The officer, who was once alive, now lies motionless on the ground. Where her head once belonged, there is now only absence, replaced by a pool of crimson blood.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Shit…”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>The clowns stare at the lifeless corpse… Eventually, they exchange a nonchalant shrug before continuing with their merry way. It's best for you to leave the scene before anyone arrives.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.c3>You see a familiar officer being harassed by a clown while she is diligently patrolling the area. Despite her efforts to maintain a composed demeanor, you occasionally do notice her furrowed eyebrows.</EventText.sadashikira.c3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.c2>Her tired eyes glances towards you when she sees you approaching.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1>“Why is there a clown following you?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.c2>“I don’t know but it has been pestering me for days now.” She replies.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2>“Can’t you just arrest the clown?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.c1>“Negative. So far the clown has not done anything illegal other than harassing me.” She states in an exhausted tone, brushing off the clown's persistent attempts to engage her.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.c1>Slowly her weary eyes lit up with life as she says, “Wait, maybe you can help me with this…”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1> “Can you convince the security in-charge of this outpost to give a warrant to arrest this clown?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Why not ask them yourself?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I have tried getting a warrant a while back but they rejected my proposal...  Since the head of security isn’t fond of my presence, someone like you might have a better chance in convincing them.” She remarks.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Sure, I can give it a try.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No, I don’t have time to deal with this.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Report back as soon as you can. I will be waiting nearby.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>As you approach the head of security, he grumbles, “What is it now? I’m rather busy at the moment.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>“Can you give a warrant of arrest to somebody in this outpost?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>He snaps at your question, “Is this about the clown bothering that inspector again? Didn’t I say no to that request already?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Why did you reject the request?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Listen, the clown has not disturbed anyone else on this station except for that bloody inspector who visited a week ago. It’s not worth wasting my time making an arrest warrant on that clown, especially when the officer will be leaving in a few days anyway.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Well, the clown has been assaulting other people recently, you just aren’t aware of it.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Really? Why haven't my officers informed me of this... Blast it all! Fine, take this and deliver it to the officer. She'll handle the clown's arrest herself." With that, he retrieves the warrant of arrest documents and passes them to you.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Take the documents and leave.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“You’re back. Did you manage to get a warrant?” She asks.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“I did. Here are the papers.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She takes the document and after reading it thoroughly, she breaks into a faint smile. “Everything looks good. Not sure how you convinced them but you saved me a lot of trouble. Here, take this.” She then hands you a few hundred mks.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Thanks for your help. Now, I must return to my duties." She declares, shifting her cold gaze toward the clown as she reaches for her stun baton. Upon witnessing her menacing action, the clown hastily flees in fear for safety.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“I’m sorry, I wasn’t able to get one.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>She sighs softly, “That’s fine. I appreciate your attempt in helping me. I’ll try to address this issue with them once more.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>“Good luck.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>She gives you a firm nod and resumes her patrol while the clown faithfully trailing her every move.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>“I have guards stationed throughout the entire station at this very moment and so far I have not received any complaints regarding the clown. So for your information, I am very much aware of what’s going on in this station. If you have nothing further to discuss, I suggest you scram and let me do my work.” He asserts.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Won’t the clown go after one of your subordinates once the officer leaves?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>He pauses his tasks, contemplating your words for a moment. "You make a good point... It's hard to predict the clown’s next move. Fine, I'll provide you with the arrest warrant. Pass it on to the officer, and she'll handle the rest." With that, he retrieves the arrest warrant documents and passes them to you.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>He dismisses the concern with a shrug. “Eh, when that happens, we’ll deal with it. Rest assured, we will arrest the clown if they harass anyone else. Now if there is nothing else you want to say, I will get back to my work.”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>“The clown is harassing someone in your outpost, isn’t that YOUR concern to begin with?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>“What are you trying to say exactly?” The security officer glares at you.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>“What if news reaches the coalition that you refused to assist your colleague? It wouldn't reflect well on your name, would it?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>He narrows his eyes as he speaks harshly, “Fine, I get what you mean… I’ll give you the arrest warrant.” He quickly gets the documents and hands them over to you. “Now get out of my sight! I already got reports to do and soon another one will be coming.” He grumbles irritably.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c2>“Ha! You must be funny to think they would care about a small matter like this. Now if you got nothing better to say, I suggest you scram unless you want a beating from me.” He retorts.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o3.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c2>She lets out a sigh before responding, “Understood. I’ll find a way to handle this matter on my own. Thank you for your time.” With that, she resumes her patrol while the clown follows suit behind her.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o2>“Aren’t you bothered by the clown?”</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3.o2.c1>“I am but I can’t do anything about it.” She replies.</EventText.sadashikira.o3.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o3>Ignore them and continue your journey.</EventText.sadashikira.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.c4>You stumble upon an aftermath scene of a fight. With a body lying down on the floor and another person standing near them.</EventText.sadashikira.c4>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4>Move closer.</EventText.sadashikira.o4>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.c1>The person notices your presence and quickly dashes away from the area, leaving you behind with the mess.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1>Check up on the person lying on the floor.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.c1>She is still breathing but unconscious and bruised. Not only that, you find her rather familiar… In fact, she is one of the military officers you met a while back on an outpost.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1>Attempt to wake her up.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.c1>You nudge her in an attempt to wake her up but she remains unresponsive. </EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1>Attempt to wake her up again.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>You try to shake her to wake her up but she still remains unresponsive.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>Slap her face to wake her up.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>You slap her as hard as you can across her face and all that does is leave a red handprint mark on her cheek. You get a feeling that she is out cold for good.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Search her body to find something to wake her up.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Do nothing and leave.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.c1>You search her and find a combat stimulant and a radio. You could try waking her by administering the stimulant or you could use the radio to call for help. Then again, with no one watching, you could steal her wallet and medicine.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1>Administer the combat stim on the officer.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>A few seconds pass before she jolts up to a sitting position, with her hands up as if she is ready for another fist fight. However, she scans around the room before her unfocused eyes lock onto yours.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Where’s Kumo?” She questions you directly while loosening her tense posture slightly.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>“Who is Kumo?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“A separatist captain in gray uniform. Did you see her?” She inquires.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Yes. She ran away the moment she saw me.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I see… That’s unfortunate.” She sighs while rubbing her temples to ease her headache.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What happened here?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I was trying to arrest her but I let my guard down at the last second… Didn't know her right hand was a bionic hand, so she managed to land a solid right hook to my jaw and knocked me out cold.” She replies.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Why were you trying to arrest her?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“She was part of my old crew and one of the missing members I was sent to track down. Personally, I have never worked with her before but based on what I can see, it seems like she’s gone back to siding with the separatists again.” She answers plainly.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“What is your plan now?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>“I have to inform the higher ups about this but for now, I need to gather my bearings. My head still hurts from the blow she dealt.” She responds calmly as she slowly gets up from the floor.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Do you need some help?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She raises her hand to stop you as she replies, “I'm fine, I can handle it from here.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Alright, I'll leave you to it.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She gives you a firm nod. Afterwards, she pulls out her radio and mutters something to it.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>“No. I saw no one when I arrived.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>“A lady in captain uniform?”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Affirmative.” She responds.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1>“She ran away the moment I arrived.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o1.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2>Use her radio to call for help.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>You take her radio and call for assistance. It does not take long for a security officer to rush over to the scene.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>“What happened over here?” The security officer asks while checking on their unconscious comrade.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1>”Someone knocked out this officer and ran as soon as they saw me approaching.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c1>“Must be a strong opponent if she gets knocked out cold like that… And they even slapped her in the face. God damn.” The security remarks amusingly when they notice a reddish handprint on her cheek.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>“Anyway, I'll take over from here. Thank you for your help.” The security officer says.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c2>“Damn… Must be a strong opponent if she gets knocked out cold like that…” The security officer comments.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o2>“I don't know. She was unconscious when I got here.”</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o2.c1>“Okay… I guess we’ll ask the sarge when she wakes up. Anyway, you’re free to go, I’ll take over from here.” The security officer replies.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o2.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3>Steal from the officer.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.c1>You keep the medicine and proceed to search her pockets again. Eventually, you manage to find her wallet and the money within. You quickly swipe the cash off the wallet and return the empty wallet back into her pockets.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.o1.c1>You promptly leave the room before anyone spots you.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.o1.c2>However, your actions have not gone unnoticed. “Hey! What are you doing!” A security guard yells at a distance. It is best to get away before they catch up to you.</EventText.sadashikira.o4.o1.o1.o2.o3.o1.c2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.c5>You see a well-dressed military officer sitting at a table with a bottle of liquor in her hand. She seems to be lost in her thoughts.</EventText.sadashikira.c5>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.c1>She snaps out of it when she notices you approaching her. "Hm? What is it?" The stern officer asks in a monotone voice.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1>"Are you a General?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.c1>"Negative, I am... Was a Commissar on board a submarine called Sorrowful. However, I recently resigned from my position." She answers, taking a swig of her liquor.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1>"Commissar? As in a person in charge of the security department?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.c1>"Affirmative." She nods in acknowledgement.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1>"Wait, then why did you resign from your job?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.c1>She pauses, before letting out a heavy sigh. "I have my own reasons... Especially after what I saw in the Eye of Europa..."</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1>"You've been to the Eye of Europa? What's in it?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"We've been near but we did not enter it. An EMP shockwave hit our submarine and left us drifting in the abyss. I remember looking through the periscope... The glowing light and the visions it gave... It was as if death awaits for those who enters... Thankfully we managed to fix our submarine and docked onto the nearest outpost for safety."</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"So, what's your plan now?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"I don't know... I didn't think that far ahead." She answers rather honestly.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>"Why not join us? We are planning to go to the Eye of Europa and we could use someone like you."</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She slams the bottle of liquor onto the table. “Did you not hear what I just said? Dammit, why is everyone so obsessed with the Eye?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Come on, are you not curious about what's in the Eye?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She seems to hesitate for a moment, before responding, “I am curious but is it really worth the risk?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“You never know, maybe the Eye has something that can obliterate the world? Don't you want to secure it?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She gives you a hard stare as she replies seriously. “Hm… If there was a weapon capable of doing that, I would. However, I will not go after it with mere speculation.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Is there any way I can convince you to join us?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She takes a swig of her drink and leans back slightly on her seat. “Negative. I have submitted my application to the HR manager, I’m sure someone from the coalition will give me a new assignment soon.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>“Oh well, it was nice meeting you.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>"Hold up, before you go.” She calls out, grabbing one of the bottles of alcohol from the table and offers it to you. “Here, take it. I'm not planning to finish all of these, so it's better to give it to someone else.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>Take the drink and thank her.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>She gives you a nod and signals you to leave with her hand as she silently resumes her drinking.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>Reject the drink.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>“Hm… I guess it's not for everybody.” She mutters, placing the bottle back on the table. Before she resumes her drinking, she signals you to leave with her hand.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Life without risk is not worth living, don’t you agree?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>The officer shakes her head at your remark. “Not everyone risks their life for amusement, some would prefer to live a life in peace. After all, I should know this since I risk my life every day in my line of work.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>“Well, good luck with your endeavors, I will take my leave.”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>After bidding farewell, the officer returns to her drink. Yet, just as you depart, a clown inexplicably approaches the former commissar, pestering her with a toy hammer. It's hard not to feel sympathy for the officer, who seems unable to catch a break from the constant disruptions.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o1.o1.o1.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2>“Let me guess, your captain was probably called Sorrow because he was sad and depressed all the time?”</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2.c1>The officer’s face maintains an expressionless look as she gives you an intimidating gaze. You got a feeling she will not reply to your remark.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2.c1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2.o1>"No? Not funny? Anyway, why did you resign from your job?"</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o1.o2.o1>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o2>"Oh nothing ma'am, just passing by."</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o2>
  <EventText.sadashikira.o5.o2.c1>She acknowledges your comment and signals you to move along as she continues to drink her liquor.</EventText.sadashikira.o5.o2.c1>
</infotexts>